Hey Dylan, uh, welcome to Chicago.
Congratulations. Uh, what was your
pre-draft process like with with the
Bears, uh, getting to know Ryan Ples and
Ben Johnson, and what do you know about
the franchise before that?
>> Um, so my pre-draft process really at
the combine, I had a a formal with them
that went really well. Um, I feel like I
really connected with all the guys
there. Um, and then I hadn't talked to
them too much, but I knew that they had
a lot of interest in me. So, um, that
was kind of most of the the
conversations that we had. And, uh, I
mean, I know I know a little bit about
the Bears history. Like, I grew up not
too not too far away from Chicago. So,
um, I know I know a decent amount there.
>> Dan,
>> Dylan, uh, how do you kind of recap your
interception against Penn State and and
kind of what that was as a signature
moment for you?
>> Uh, that that moment I think was just
incredible. like the way to to to seal
the game like that was amazing and just
do it for the team. Um we've been
talking about that same play uh from
like a defensive aspect like the play
call and then that offensive formation
like we've we've repped both of those
together in practice and for it to show
up in the game um just how the coaches
kind of predicted was amazing.
>> You've talked about kind of your
recognition being a strength of yours.
How do you strengthen that over the
course of your your playing life and how
did it get to the level it's at now? Um
really just when I keep improving my
process and my preparation like how I
watch film um and taking notes, writing
stuff down. So I had I had two separate
notebooks. So I had a notebook just for
opponent scout and I had a notebook
where I wrote everything down. So I
write everything in one notebook and
then I would kind of compile it and what
I needed to study, what I needed to know
in another one so I could study that um
before the game.
>> Kevin,
>> hey Dylan, congratulations. Um, a lot of
the coaches have talked about your
versatility. Uh, how did you kind of
hone that and what are all the different
positions you you kind of can see
yourself helping out uh the Bears in?
>> Um, well, I mean, at Purdue, I played
mostly in the post, so I was playing
free safety there, but then Oregon, we
played field and boundary. And in
Oregon's defense, you're asked to do
literally everything. So, um, I mean,
I'm rolling down in the box. I'm
rotating different cover threes. I'm
playing the half. I'm playing quarters.
So I I got really comfortable playing a
lot of different uh coverages and
different positions. So I really good uh
playing field and then I could play
boundaries. So doing those and then I
cross trainined nickel um in the
offseason too. So I felt I felt pretty
comfortable moving between all those
positions because I I knew everything on
the the back end.
>> Courtney.
>> Hey Dylan. The Bears have made a pretty
big emphasis this offseason by adding
speed to their defense. Um, I know you
ran a 435 530. So, like two-part
question here. Was that the time that
you was that a goal time? Was that
faster than you expected? And what do
you think that speed can do to bring how
do you feel like you can bring your
speed to the NFL and how it translates
to the NFL game?
>> Uh, going into the combine training, I
set a goal of being 4-3. Um, and then to
go out there and do that kind of
surpassed even my expectations at that
point. Like, I knew I knew in my heart I
was going to get 4-3. Um, but I didn't
know what exactly it would be. Um, and I
feel like speed is very very interesting
because there's there's normal speed and
then there's gameplay and speed. So the
more you can process and recognize the
faster you can play in game closer to
your true speed.
>> Sean,
>> hey Dylan, congrats. Um, I'm wondering
if you could just kind of take us
through tonight. What is this whole
experience like being there and and
hearing your name?
>> It's been incredible. I mean, it's it's
a once in a lifetime moment. So, I'm
very glad that I came here and got to
experience that with the family and the
other people that have helped me get to
this point.
>> Josh,
>> hi. Welcome to Chicago. Uh, just curious
how familiar you are with Dennis Allen
and how you hear yourself as a
playmaker.
>> I'm sorry. Can you say that again?
>> Yeah, sure. I was just wondering how
familiar you are with Dennis Allen and
how you hear yourself as a playmate or
as a ball hawk in the secondary.
Um, I'm not super familiar with Dennis
Allen, but I'm sure we'll get to know
each other quite well. Um, and then in
the backhand and just really if I can
utilize my speed, I can go get that
ball.
>> Dion,
>> hi Dylan. Welcome. We're excited to have
you. Um, you you mentioned just the
journey that you've taken to go from
Purdue and out to Oregon. Like, how how
do you feel like you're prepared to take
this NFL step and ready to kind of hit
the ground running? I feel like making
the the leap to to Oregon was kind of
preparing me for the next level already.
Like I'm going to a new place, new
coaches, new scheme, new environment.
Um, so I'm kind of used to that change
and I know how to make it um and what
works for me and what doesn't. So I'm
kind of able to to grow from that last
experience and um I think hit the ground
running.
>> Last two. Dan,
>> Dylan, two quick ones. What's the uh the
chain you got on and who gave that to
you? Uh, we got the Bears chain and then
someone in the crowd gave it to me when
I went out and took a pick with the
fans.
>> Okay. Also, I know you've you've
referenced Palamalo as a guy that you
looked up to. What What drew you to his
game when you were younger?
>> Really, his versatility and um I liked
watching some of his interviews like if
he knew where the ball was going, he
would go switch positions with that
player so that he could be in on a play
so he could have an impact for the team.
So, just having that knowledge of the
defense, but then also the understanding
what the offense is trying to do.
Last one, Courtney.
>> Dylan, really quick, back to your speed.
Have you always been fast? Is this
something that like as a kid you realize
like I'm just faster than everybody
else? Is this something you had to
really work on?
>> I have always been fast, but I feel like
it's really kind of picked up being in
college. Um, I know my brothers would
joke. I used to like race down the
driveway
all the time, like racing them or racing
like the car on the way home from
school, like some of that stuff.
>> Awesome. Thank you so much, Dylan.
Congratulations.
>> Oh, thank you.
>> We'll see you tomorrow.